finicity.com 2017-06-02

# Privacy Policy - Finicity

#### Your Privacy Is Important To Us

_Date of Last Revision: May 23, 2014_

Applicable law requires us to provide users who subscribe to our service a description of our information collection and sharing practices. This Statement of Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) specifically describes how we handle your personally identifiable information, and applies to financial products and services provided by Finicity.

#### Information Collection and Use

##### Use of Information

You license us to use the contact information (name, address, phone number, and e-mail address) and personal financial information (account names and numbers, passwords, and PINs) you share with us for the limited purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy.  We will not sell, share, or rent your contact information or personal financial information except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy.  We will not share your personally identifiable information with third parties except as required by law, to fulfill your request for service, or as otherwise outlined in this Privacy Policy.  To maximize the value of our services, we may request or collect information from you when you use our services or visit our websites.  Whenever we ask for additional or optional information, we identify those fields appropriately so you may know what information is required to provide the requested service.  This Privacy Policy describes the scope and purpose of our information collection practices, and the circumstances under which your information may be used or disclosed.

##### Service Enrollment and Usage

When you register to use on of our services, you are entitled to use certain services on our website. You will be asked to select a user name and password and provide us your e-mail address and zip code or postal code.  We use your user name and password to verify your identity, which is required to give you access to our service.  We ask you to provide us your mother’s maiden name or another unique identifier in order to identify you in case you forget your password.  For access to financial, investment, and credit card statement download services, we ask you to provide additional information such as a account numbers and a personal identification numbers (PINs).  We use this information to verify your accounts with your financial institutions and to establish the requested service with the financial institutions, brokerage houses, and credit card companies of your choice.  If you subscribe to a service requiring payment, we ask for your credit card number or checking account information to process your initial payment and all subsequent payments.  We will use your e-mail address as our primary source of contact with you regarding our service.  In the event you receive Finicity newsletters you no longer wish to receive, you may unsubscribe to them by following the instructions provided in each e-mail newsletter.

##### Technical and Product Support

In order to provide you with technical and product support, we ask for your name and e-mail address. We may use your contact information to contact you regarding service updates or specific support questions.  We may also contact you for additional opportunities to provide feedback on our products and services, unless you request not to receive such communications. If we are unable to access your account at your financial institution, we may use your personal financial information to maintain or repair the connection to your financial institution.

##### Contests and Surveys

From time to time, we may offer you the option to participate in contests or surveys.  If you would like to participate, we may ask you for contact information, preferences, or other information.  This information may be used to conduct research, improve our offerings, or award prizes.  Our contests may have separate rules that describe how the information you supply will be used in each case. ** ** ****

##### Information About Your Computer or Browser

Finicity collects information about your computer or web browser in order to analyze trends and administer our websites. We gather broad demographic information so we can provide our users with a better web experience and appropriate products and services, and also to format e-mail messages to align best with your computer’s capabilities. This information is collected in a generic aggregate format and is not linked to personally identifiable information.

##### Aggregated Data About User Transactions

Notwithstanding any provision of this Privacy Policy to the contrary, Finicity collects and may share or publicly disclose compiled, aggregated data concerning financial transactions of its users.  This information is collected in a generic aggregate format and, to the extent it is shared or disclosed, will not contain any personally identifiable information.

##### Links to Other Sites

Finicity websites may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Finicity is not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site, and to read the privacy policy of every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Finicity websites. Co-branded sites are clearly identified by both a Finicity logo and a partner’s logo.  On these sites Finicity and its partners may collect personal information. Please review the privacy policies of our partners to determine how they will use the information they collect. Finicity is not responsible for the information practices of any third parties.

##### Web Site Cookie Usage

In order to serve you better and protect your account information, we use “cookies,” nuggets of data that are stored on your hard drive as a file.  We use cookies to verify your identity while you are using our websites.  Cookies make it easier, faster, and more secure for you to log into and use our websites.  Cookies do not compromise privacy or personally identify users.  Their data is usually stored on your computer’s hard drive as a file or folder called “Cookies,” and you can delete this file anytime you choose.  The cookies used on our websites are valid only for the current session and shortly become invalid.  Cookies created by one site will work only with that specific site.  Site A, for example, cannot read cookies generated by Site B and then use that information for purposes for which it was not intended.

##### Referrals

If users elect to use our referral service to inform others about our site or products, we ask them for a name, phone number, and e-mail address for themselves and for the person being referred.  Finicity will automatically send the referred person a one-time e-mail, or telephone them one time inviting them to visit the site or make a purchase.  Finicity stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time e-mail or making this one-time phone call.  The referred person may contact [Finicity Support](mailto:support@finicity.com) to request the removal of this information from the referral database.

##### Former Customers

We treat information concerning our former customers the same way we treat information about our current customers, as outlined in this Privacy Policy.

##### Children

Because of the financial nature of our business, our websites are not designed to appeal to children under the age of 18.  Therefore, we don’t knowingly attempt to solicit or receive any information from minors.

#### Access to Your Information

Finicity does not share your personally identifiable information with third parties except as described in this Privacy Policy, or except as you have otherwise agreed. The information you provide us will be shared only under limited circumstances.  These include:

##### With Finicity-Approved Partners

If you have enrolled after coming to Finicity through a Finicity-approved partner site, Finicity will provide to the approved partner a copy of your name, mailing address, and e-mail address.  Finicity will NOT provide any approved partner your financial information or account information (such as user name and password), but only the information listed above.  Finicity-approved partners are restricted by contract from sharing this personal information with any third parties, and from using this information other than in accordance with their published privacy policies.

##### With Service Providers

In some cases, we will employ or work with service providers such as marketing or security consultants, temporary workers, third-party software developers, or outsourcers to complete a business process or provide a service on our behalf.  We may use service providers to deliver products, to offer online software applications, or to send e-mails on our behalf.  While this may require that we share some information, we will share only information the service provider must have to perform the requested services.  For example, a service provider who delivers products on our behalf would need to have a delivery address, but not financial information.  These service providers are strictly prohibited by contract from using your information for any purpose other than to act on our behalf.

##### For Legal Reasons

In some cases we may be required to disclose certain information to comply with the law, an investigation, or a legal process, such as a court order or subpoena.

##### In Case of a Sale of Business

Your information may be transferred in connection with a sale, merger, transfer, exchange, or other disposition (whether of assets, stock or otherwise) of all or a portion of a business operated by Finicity or its affiliates.

##### Information Opt-out Choice

When Finicity sends you information, we give you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving further information.  Simply use the unsubscribe feature provided within each e-mail, or contact [Finicity Support](mailto:support@finicity.com). We may send you site and service announcement updates.  You are not able to unsubscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about service.  We communicate with you by e-mail regarding issues relating to your account or to provide requested services.

##### Security Safeguards

We employ industry-standard physical, electronic, and procedural security safeguards to help protect the personally identifiable information you have provided to us from loss, misuse, or unauthorized alteration.

You are responsible for protecting the secrecy of your Finicity password.  We recommend that you do not store secure pages in your cache or leave your computer unattended while you are logged in to any Finicity online service or while enrolling on the Finicity website.

##### Correcting/Updating Personal Information

On our website, we provide you the opportunity to update or correct your account, financial, and credit card information. You may review and update your contact information (name, address, and e-mail address) by contacting [Finicity Support](mailto:support@finicity.com). You are responsible to keep on file with Finicity, current personal and financial information in order to use Finicity’s services.

##### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy or our practices with respect to how we use personally identifiable information at any time in our sole discretion without further notice.  We will post the revisions to our website and indicate the date of the last revision.

##### How to Contact Us

Questions regarding this Privacy Policy, our information practices, or other aspects of privacy on our websites should be directed to [Finicity Support.](mailto:support@finicity.com)

Finicity, the Finicity logo, In2M, and the In2M logo are trademarks or registered trademarks of Finicity Corporation.
